Now that we can successfully stop the
form from submitting, now we can control
what we want to do with it once it does
submit. So, for example, here um I have
now brought back in my Axios library and
down here I can say Axios.
And I'm going to post to my um API.
And what do I want to post? Well, I want
to post the data from my form.
So, um, just to demonstrate this, I
could say name,
username,
and I'm going to put I'm going to
hardcode for now and password
and then set that. So, if I save this
and I put test and hit submit, if I come
over here to the DBJSON, you can see
that it put in the username and password
that I requested. All right, I'm going
to delete this data from my database for
now and save it. So you can see that the
API did in fact respond. Well, now I
need to get data out of the form. So if
I want to get the username, then I have
to say document.query
selector and then I have to find it um
by its name and that can be a pain. And
then I'd have to do that for usern for
password as well.
But imagine if my form got longer. That
is a whole bunch of query selectors I'm
going to need to be doing. So, what I'm
going to show you in the next video is
how you can do it all on one